ZiMuZu
倾情奉献
翻译
草草
煮粥达人
翻译
磁芯章鱼X
滚成一个团子
翻译
某羽
showeryhe
翻译
木浅
潇湘月影
时间轴
Kallen   今   兜兜兜爹
特效
宝宝
电脑狂人
第二季
第五集
校对&总监
草草
后期
饿得慌
顾问
somehacker
我终于想到
I finally thought of something
达拉斯比奥斯汀好的地方了
I like more about Dallas than Austin.
你在达拉斯
You're in Dallas.
该死的
Son of a bitch.
莎拉  没事吧
Sara? Everything all right?
卡罗琳  我是莎拉
Caroline, it's Sara.
让我爸爸接电话
Put my dad on the phone.
我收到你寄来的礼物了
Got your little present in the mail.
你律师寄来的
The one from your lawyers.
即使我想  你就这么做吗
Even if I wanted to, this is how you do it?
问都不问问我
You don't even ask me about it?
不  这没得商量
No, this isn't up for debate.
可不是  爸爸
Yeah, no kidding, Dad.
我才是经历了那一切的人
You know, I was the one who went through it.
你什么时候才能不这样对我
So when are you gonna stop treating me like this?
我不是小孩了
I'm not a kid.
停止  这就停止
Just stop. Stop now.
婚前协议
因为我相信他  我希望他知道这点
Because I trust him and I want him to know that.
他不该受这种委屈  我不会那样对他
He deserves better. I'm not gonna do that to him.
是啊  网络很快
I know, the network's fast,
但我们没有最大限度利用它的东西
but we don't have anything that maximizes it.
我们有辆赛车  却只在闲置着
We have this... racecar and it's just idling.
我们有赛道  我们需要一辆赛车
Well, we have a race track. What we need is a racecar.
你真的好讨厌
You're really annoying.
但这就将是我们的赛车
But this will be our racecar.
两位玩家  第一视角游戏
Two player, first person game,
拨号上网  在线游戏
online, over dial-up.
我们还得考虑清楚游戏设定
We still have to figure out what it's about.
是啊  我们会的
What it's about. Yeah, we will.
我们会想出来的
Between the two of us.
还有我们一流的团队
And our crack team.
这将是非常出色的游戏
It will be excellent game,
就像从可怜的小男孩手里偷面包
like steal the bread from the weak little boy.
我模仿得很像
It is good impersonation I do.
如果你是在模仿被派去杀莎拉·康纳的机器人的话
If you were impersonating the cyborg sent to kill Sarah Connor.
对了  那个今天发行
Oh, damn, that came out today.
-对啊  -嗯  我想去买
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah, I want to go pick it up.
我阳光海岸的朋友说好替我留一份
My friend at Suncoast was gonna reserve a copy.
几点了
What time is it?
我得走了
I gotta go.
我要是迟到了  我老板会骂死我的
If I'm late, my boss is gonna have my ass.
她听上去好可恶
Oh, she sounds like such a bitch.
可不是吗
Oh, you have no idea.
你的衣服  马上给我
Your clothes, give them to me now.
别闹啦
Stop with the impressions.
你  我  今晚看《终结者》
You, me, "Terminator," Tonight.
好
Okay.
早上好  美女
Mornin', sunshine.
你才回家吗
You just headin' home?
就回去几小时
Uh, just for a couple hours.
好姑娘
Attagirl.
好好睡一觉
Now get some shut-eye.
我会确保这地方离了你不会烧毁
I'll make sure the place doesn't burn down without you.
好吧
All right.
早上好
Hey, good morning.
熬夜了  要点咖啡吗
Long night? You want some coffee?
我有点想喝啤酒  是不是不太好
I kind of want a beer. Is that bad?
当然不会  忙了一整天  我也会想喝两杯
Hell, no. A long day at work, I'd have two.
-孩子们呢  -在刷牙
- Where are the girls? - They're brushing their teeth.
感觉太棒了
Oh, that is too good.
那边一切还好吧
Everything going okay over there?
嗯  非常棒
Yeah, it's amazing.
社区扩张很快
You know, Community's expanding so fast.
工作量很大  但是我想做的工作
It's just a lot of work, but it's work I want to be doing.
对了
Oh, shoot.
我们应该联系
You know, we need to get in touch
一下那边的人
with somebody over at what's it called.
他们还没把首张发票寄过来
They haven't sent us our first invoice
我们得算算账
and we need to figure out billing.
这个嘛
Oh, well,
他们肯定会发些什么过来的
I'm sure they'll probably send something over, you know?
嗯  我只是想把合同落到纸面上
Yeah, I just want to make sure we get this deal in writing.
简直像天上掉馅饼一样不真实
It seems almost too good to be true.
那好  那我和他谈谈
Right, well, I'll talk to him.
你要忙的事不少了
You know, you've got enough on your plate.
就是你真心想做的事
You know, stuff you actually want to be doing.
-嗯  -对了  我有件事想和你说说
- Yeah-- - Oh, I wanted to talk to you about this.
我在考虑做
I've been thinking about doing something
订制电脑的生意
with this made-to-order computer business.
是啊  挺好的
Yeah, you should.
怎么了
Something wrong?
没事  不小心呛着了
No, no, it just went down the wrong pipe.
话说  考虑到
You know, I think maybe with everything
之前索纳里斯那事
that's gone down with Sonaris and all,
也许我直接和他们打交道比较好
it'd be better if I could deal with them directly.
你了解卡梅伦  如果你插一手
You know Cameron. If I can keep you out of it,
她大概会对我们大发雷霆
maybe we can spare ourselves her wrath.
好  可以  没问题
Yeah, sure. No problem.
那好  能尽快安排次见面吗  比如这周
Great, so we can set something up soon? This week?
行
Yeah.
其实
You know what? Actually
那边在跟我接洽的人  就是乔
the person I've been dealing with over there is Joe.
哪个乔
Joe who?
别乱扔啊
Oh, come on, now.
躲啊
Duck!
天老爷  你穿的是睡衣吗
Gracious, is that a pajama top?
睡衣本质上是什么呢  约翰
Well, what is a pajama top, John?
如果你穿这身睡着了
I mean, if you fall asleep in that shirt,
那这就成睡衣了吗
does it become a pajama top?
所以这就不是睡衣  因为我...
And then can it ever not be a pajama top once it is--
我只是想问你买的时候没买配套睡裤吗
I'm just askin' when you bought it, did it come with bottoms?
睡裤本质上又是什么呢
What constitutes bottoms?
得  当我没问
Okay, forget I asked.
好是好  不过你知道我会说什么
Yeah, it's cool, but you know what I'm gonna say.
别这样  就是好人对坏人
Oh, come on. Look, it's good guys versus bad guys.
但他们为什么是坏人
Yeah, but why are they bad?
为什么要打他们  背景故事是什么
Why do we care? What's the context?
背景故...过山车就没有背景故事
Cont-- a roller coaster doesn't have any context.
-汤姆  -怎么  大家从过山车上下来
- Tom... - What? No one gets off Judge Roy Scream
才不会去谈论其典故  他们在乎的是刺激体验
talking about the story. They talk about the experience.
坐一趟过山车只要90秒
A roller coaster's 90 seconds long.
你得琢磨出
You have to create something
能让玩家沉迷几小时的内容来
here that's gonna consume people for hours.
-你知道我说得对  -卡梅伦
- You know I'm right. - Cameron?
我会回来的[《终结者》台词]
I'll be back.
老天  怎么了  你又想怎样
Oh, God. What? What do you want?
你也知道  我是穆特尼的老用户了
As you know, I am a long-standing Mutiny user,
所以我相信你会重视我的看法
so I trust you'll give my input the weight it is due.
-赶紧说吧  -昨天晚上
- Okay, get on with it. - Yesterday evening,
我在玩视差
I was playing "Parallax."
第8章第4关
Chapter eight, challenge four.
-在大道上  -怎么了
- On the path... - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我把谜题解开了
I solved the riddle
却没办法继续走下去
and yet I wasn't able to continue on.
要么这是个故障
Either this is a glitch or
要么就是你们剧情安排出问题了
an illogical piece of in-game storytelling.
不管怎样  我要你们退还我这几小时的费用
Whatever the case, I would like like a refund for that hour of usage.
给你钱才怪  哥们
You're not getting shit, buddy.
我们才不会
We don't give refunds for
给过不了关的笨蛋玩家退钱
people who are too thick to figure out the game,
即使我们退费  你两个月没付账了
and even if we did, you haven't paid your bill in two months,
你本来就在透支游戏时间
so you're operating on borrowed time as it is.
如果我是你  我就会回到第8章
Now, if I were you, I'd head back to chapter eight
或许想想我越来越少的水储备
and maybe consider my dwindling water reserves
看看在游戏里什么地方能补水
and see where in the game I could've replenished my supply.
再见
Bye!
-切特吗  -对
- Chet? - Yeah.
但这没道理啊
But it just makes no damn sense.
我想要杯咖啡
I want a cup of coffee...
可杯子在厨房这边
Look, cups are clear across the kitchen, huh?
看见没  那糖在哪里呢
See? Now where's the sugar?
又在厨房的另一边
Again, all the way across the kitchen.
你看  我像弹球一样来回蹦跶
Come on, man. I'm bouncing around like a damn pinball.
在这里建个咖啡站  一站解决所有需求
Now, look, create a station. One-stop, all your needs.
你明白我在说什么吗
Do you know what I'm talking about?
咖啡吗
Coffee?
天哪
Oh, God.
是效率  小子  时间就是金钱
Efficiency, son. Time is money.
天呐...出去吧
For... get outta here.
你简直太棒  博斯
You're amazing, Boz.
刚刚烦你的人是谁
Hey, who was that bothering you?
是切特  他是个用户
Oh, Chet. He's a user.
他就是个烦人鬼
He's just some pain in the ass.
垂直空间呢
What about vertical space?
我们可以设置垂直的管道
We could have these vertical tubes
让你爬上爬下
that you climb up, you drop down...
嗯  这很棒  但你知道我会说什么
Yeah, that's amazing. But you know what I'm gonna say...
嗯嗯嗯  你就看看嘛
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Just check it out.
-来看看  -那你去想吧
- Just check it out. - Well, then, figure it out.
你和你老婆撒谎了  这不是我的问题
You lied to your wife. That's not my problem.
就是你的问题  她会告诉卡梅伦的
Oh, but it is. She's gonna tell Cameron, all right?
她们想和一个西方集团的代表坐下谈谈
They want a sit-down with a representative from Westgroup.
她们要一份书面的正式合同
They want a formal agreement in writing.
你得把这事正规化
Look, you gotta make this thing legitimate.
-这不可能  -那就想办法
- That's not possible. - Well, then, make it possible.
这才三周
It's only been three weeks.
我的计划是收集数月的数据
The whole plan was to amass months of data.
-我们别无选择  -我们总有选择的
- We don't have a choice. - We've always got a choice.
我可以把穆特尼赶出网络
I can kick Mutiny off the network
再去另找一家在线服务提供商
and go to another online service.
你可以  但你不会那么做
You can, but you're not going to
因为我们说好的  对吗  乔
because we had a deal, right, Joe?
而且你会遵守约定
And you're gonna honor that agreement
因为你不是每个人口中说的
because you're not the reptilian son of a bitch
那种冷血混蛋
that everybody says you are.
-你已经变了  -这不是我的打算
- You're a changed man. - This isn't what I wanted.
如果我过早告诉维勒
If I tell Wheeler too early
而他不支持的话  整个网络就泡汤了
and he doesn't go for it, the network is done,
-穆特尼也完了  -别犯傻了
- Mutiny is done. - Snap out of it, all right?
你可是乔·麦克米伦
You're Joe MacMillan.
如果你想的话都可以撺掇他跳桥
You could talk him into jumping off a bridge if you wanted to.
下定决心  去做就好
Just decide to do it and do it.
我得走了
Look, I gotta go.
-向我保证你会...  -知道了
- Just promise me that you're gonna... - Got it.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我想先强调我之前完全不知情
I want to emphasize that I had no idea about this,
我一得知  就直接来找你了
and as soon as I found out, I came straight here.
怎么了
What?
是乔·麦克米伦在运营网络
Joe MacMillan is the person running the network.
他是戈登在公司的联络人
He's Gordon's contact at the company.
你说什么
I'm sorry?
戈登帮他设置了分时系统
Gordon helped him set up time-sharing.
以此交换穆特尼拿到优惠的合同
He insisted that Mutiny get a good deal,
-但他没告诉我  -打住
- and he didn't tell me... - Stop.
你把乔·麦克米伦放进门来了
You let Joe MacMillan in the door?
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything.
是啊  又是戈登
No, Gordon, again.
-抱歉唐娜  但他不在这里工作  -我知道
- I'm sorry, Donna, but he doesn't work here. - I know.
-我们的事轮不到他管  -我知道
- This isn't his to mess with. - I know.
他想补偿搞垮网络的那事
He wanted to make up for crashing the network.
好个道歉的方式
What a way to apologize.
他很惭愧  所以想弥补
He felt terrible. He wanted to fix it.
我知道这不算安慰
I know this isn't any consolation,
但我见过乔  他看起来...不一样了
but I sat across from Joe. He seems... different.
或许他变了
Maybe he's changed.
谢谢你的坦诚
Thank you for your honesty.
如果你不介意  我想自己待会儿
If you don't mind, I'd like a few moments to myself.
好
Okay.
从上次的检测来看
Um, based on my examination last time--
你手的平衡失调
the symmetrical weakness in your hands,
以及记忆力和注意力的测试
the memory and concentration tests,
加之你的工作经历  你曾在铅焊料环境中工作
your employment history, um, exposure to lead solder,
使用过有机溶剂  我给你做了核磁共振
and working with solvents-- I ordered the MRI.
我知道你不太喜欢做这项检测
I know you were a little ambivalent about the test,
但我很高兴我们还是做了
but I am glad that we sprung for it
因为它真是个很棒的新工具
because it really is an amazing new tool.
据放射科医生说  有两个区域
According to the radiologists, there are two areas,
非常小的区域  有萎缩迹象
very small, that show signs of atrophy.
萎缩
Atrophy?
脑损伤
Brain damage.
叫做慢性中毒性脑病
It's chronic toxic encephalopathy.
根据各种现象综合来看
Now, given this combination of clues,
这能解释你的身体症状
it explains your physical symptoms
也很可能造成了你跟我描述的
and it likely accounts for the psychological symptoms
心理问题
you described to me as well--
你的易怒和情绪波动
irritability and the mood swings.
好吧  那要怎么解决
Yeah, how do I fix it?
我很遗憾  没有治疗方法
I'm sorry to say there is no treatment.
脑组织无法自我修复
Brain tissue does not repair itself.
这个病将是永久性的
This will be a permanent condition.
但我觉得没事
But I feel fine.
今后会发生什么
What the hell's gonna happen now?
你的症状可能会加重
Well, your symptoms could likely progress.
-还会加重吗  -这是多年间
- This could get worse? - This was years of
毒素在你血液中渐渐积累的结果
slow accumulation of these toxins in your blood.
但鉴于此  你的症状如今加速显现出来
But in light of that, the fact that your symptoms have accelerated
说明你可能
would indicate that
还没有到最糟糕的状态
you likely haven't seen the worst of this yet.
我很抱歉  戈登
I am sorry, Gordon.
卡梅伦怎么了
So, what's going on with Cameron?
你记得乔·麦克米伦吗
Do you remember Joe MacMillan?
-记得啊  眉毛将军  -什么
- Sure, Admiral Eyebrows. - What?
我们这么叫他  你不这么叫吗
That's what we called him. You didn't call him that?
以前不  但以后会了
No, but I will now.
总之  原来他是网络的运营商
Anyway, turns out he's the one who's running the network.
真糟  她为了躲那个疯子  才搞了叛乱[穆特尼]
That sucks. She mutinied to get away from that psycho.
你跟谁聊天呢  莱夫
Who are you talking to, Lev?
没谁
Nobody.
不关你的事  就是个朋友
It's none of your business. It's just a friend.
你在跟谁聊天  莱夫
Who you talking to, Lev?
就是我在社区里认识的一个人
It's just a guy I met in one of the forums.
我们一直在聊  他喜欢治疗乐队[英国乐队]
We've-- we've been talking. He likes the Cure.
-你在跟他调情  -那又怎样
- You've been flirting. - So?
莱夫  这很好  非常好
Lev, this is good. This is really good.
我们要做一个可以在网上认识人的聊天室
We're gonna make a room where you can meet people online.
-认识  -对
- Meet? - Yes.
-姑娘吗  -对
- Like girls? - Yes!
我们做一个交友聊天室  让大家结识
We'll do a personals room where you meet
然后再进入私密聊天室  像约会一样
and then you go into a private room, like a date.
是莱夫给了她灵感
She got the idea from Lev
因为他一直在网上跟人聊天
'cause he's been talking to someone online.
这可好
Oh, great.
我还一直活在过去呢
You see, I've been living in the past,
按照传统  带女人出去吃饭
taking a woman out to dinner like we used to do.
-你有约会呀  博斯  -真不明白
- You got a date, Boz? - Now, I'm not sure
你们为什么对此这么震惊又怀疑
why that news is met with such shock and disbelief.
你看来是在跟男孩子聊天呢  莱夫
Looks like you're talking to a fella there, Lev.
是啊
Yeah.
这样啊  好吧
Yeah, okay.
原来你是
No, so you're...
没事  这完全...好吧
no, that's completely, uh... yeah.
我有个亲戚也是
Oh, hell, I got a cousin.
很好
Good.
我得再来杯咖啡
I'm gonna get another coffee here.
-嗯  -唐娜  戈登找你
- Yeah. - Hey, Donna, it's Gordon!
喂
Hello?
-亲爱的  -什么事
- Hey, sweetie. - What's up?
-我... -我们给私人聊天室起什么名
- I was, uh... - What are we gonna call the private rooms?
不知道  双人小桌
I don't know, A Table For Two?
-好恶  -那你自己想吧
- Barf. - Okay, fine, then you figure it out.
抱歉  你说什么
Sorry, what were you saying?
你在哪  周围好吵
Where are you? It's loud.
我...刚开了电视
I've, uh... I just got the TV on.
今晚出来怎么样  就我们俩
Why don't we go out tonight, just the two of us?
不带孩子
No kids?
我们好久没
It's been a while since
享受二人世界了
we spent some time together just you and me.
-唐娜  -抱歉我走神了
- Donna? - Yeah, sorry. I lost you for a second.
主意不错  可是我们刚有个新点子
That sounds great. We just really hit on something
可能会工作到很晚  所以
and I think we're probably gonna be working late, so...
能理解
Yeah, yeah, of course.
那这周末可以吗
Um, but maybe this weekend sometime?
-当然  -抱歉  我要去干活儿了
- Sure. - Sorry, look, I gotta jump off,
回家见
but I'll see you at home, okay?
-爱你  再见  -我也爱...
- I love you, bye. - Yeah, yeah, I love you t...
汤姆  走吗
Hey, Tom, you coming?
-不错哦  -我要副驾
- Sounds cool. - Shotgun.
-嗯  -烦人
- Yeah. - Aw, man!
你知不知道她怎么了
Hey, um, do you know what's going on with her?
-卡梅伦  -前任的烦心事
- With Cameron? - Stuff with her ex.
一言难尽
It's a long story.
走吧  出发啦
Come on, let's go.
-狗子快冲  -你才狗呢
- Come on, sobachka. - You dog.
钥匙带上
Grab my keys!
终结者
卡梅
Hey, Cam.
干什么呢
What's shakin'?
天呐  破椅子
Oh, Jesus! This stupid chair.
卡梅
Hey, Cam?
-卡梅  -什么事
- Cam? - What?
咱俩谈谈
Come on, let's talk.
我计算了
I've calculated the cost
你抽出来每桶石油的成本
of every barrel of oil you pull out of the ground.
最开始的盈利需要很多投入
It takes an awful lot of money to make that first dollar.
用现有的主机提供分时服务
Using your existing mainframe for time-sharing,
就不需要你支出
there's no cost to you.
这一整片汪洋都是银子
There's an ocean of money out there
而你已经钻了井
and you have already drilled the wells.
大家谈论起计算机革命
People talk about the computer revolution
好像这都过去了
as if it were a thing of the past,
可我从小就围着IBM
but I grew up running around IBM.
这一行深入我的血液
This business is in my blood,
相信我
and believe me when I tell you,
这场革命还没开始
the revolution hasn't even started yet.
这听起来
I think it sounds...
挺有前途
promising.
我就知道你会理解
I thought you would.
所以三周前我就开干了
That's why I did it three weeks ago.
我改进了主机
I retrofitted the mainframe.
把网络租给了一家新兴公司穆特尼
I sold the time to an exciting company called Mutiny.
仅三周  它们就呈现了稳定的增长
In three weeks, they've shown steady growth
而且还会继续扩张
and will only continue to expand.
这或许能成为西方集团放弃挖掘过去
This could be the moment when Westgroup stops digging in the past
开始打造未来的时刻
and starts building the future.
而你...什么都不用做
All you have to do... is nothing.
三周的数据  这不算什么
Three weeks of data, that's not much.
-但趋势大好  -也许吧  坐下  乔
- The trend will continue. - Maybe. Have a seat, Joe.
这都是你背着我干的
So, you did all this behind my back.
不小的赌博啊
That was quite a gamble.
西方集团规模巨大
You know, Westgroup is a huge operation.
但是  这种大规模公司
However, one resource sorely lacking
唯一紧缺的资源  就是动力
in a company of this size is hunger.
这里的人都满足而开心
Everybody here is fat and happy.
但你呢
But you?
我觉得你是那种永不满足的人
You strike me as the kind of guy that isn't ever satisfied.
你不开心  这是能生钱的
You aren't happy, and I can turn that into money.
这样一来  你就要离开数据录入部了吧
I assume this takes you out of Data Entry.
是的  我要当网络主管
It would. I would be the network administrator
主管网络出租  还有硬件维护
managing the sales of the time, the hardware upkeep.
新头衔是不是也要涨薪
And I suppose a nice raise comes along with a new title.
不用  先让我向你证明这能成功再说
No raise. Let me show you that it works first.
这些莎拉都知道吗
Sara knew all about this, huh?
居然完全瞒过了我
She's got some poker face.
是啊
Yeah.
我想先见见他们公司的人
I just want to have a meeting with somebody from,
叫什么来着  穆特尼
what was it? Mutiny?
明晚就安排个见面吧
Let's have a sit-down tomorrow night.
我7点要飞去阿拉斯加  走前见个面
I'm flying up to Alaska around 7:00, but we can meet before then.
这不用你担心  客户我可以应酬
Uh, you don't have to worry. I can handle the client.
我没担心  明晚见面
Oh, I'm not worried. We'll meet tomorrow night.
想和我做生意的人
I never go into business with anyone
我都要先见一面
without looking them in the eye first.
我想杀了他
Well, I want to kill him.
我知道你不喜欢乔  我也是
I know you don't like Joe. Neither do I.
我也想看他倒霉
I'd like to see him punched in the balls as much as anybody,
但他是个生意人  而且做得不赖
but he's a businessman, and not a bad one.
搞出了巨人  还拉我入伙了
Put together Giant, got me onboard.
那倒霉盒子就是场灾难
That box was an abomination.
严格从商业角度来看
From a strictly commercial standpoint,
当时撤出你的系统是正确的做法
pulling your operating system was the right move.
那台机器  对我意义重大
That machine, it meant a lot to me.
虽然称不上艺术  但确实是好商品
It wasn't art, but it was sound business,
穆特尼的问题就在于
and one thing about Mutiny is
太艺术  但缺乏商业性
you got a whole lot of the former, not much of the latter.
再说了  现在他做的也正是你想要的
Look, to top it all off, you got Joe right where you want him.
不是吗
You kidding me?
他想要求你原谅  想要弥补你
He wants forgiveness. He wants to do right by you.
我只是觉得我们又陷入了他的什么计划
I just feel like we're part of some plan that he has.
唯一一个我相信
The only person I trust to get
能看清乔·麦克米伦的人  就是你
an accurate read on Joe MacMillan-- that's you.
你得去看清他的想法
You gotta look him in the eye.
如果我不满意我看到的呢
And if I don't like what I see?
那你就杀了他
Then you kill him.
笑一个
Smile!
你为什么不跳舞
Why aren't you dancing?
我有脑损伤
I have brain damage!
没听说过
Oh, never heard of them.
我觉得我要死了
I think I'm dying!
我也是
Oh, me, too!
你为什么不在之前告诉我
Why didn't you tell me beforehand?
以防万一不成功
In case it didn't work out.
我不想让你看到我失败
I didn't want to fall on my face in front of you.
话说你是怎么做到的啊
How did you even do it?
戈登帮我设置了系统
Gordon helped me with the setup.
他改装了一部分机器
He did some of the hardware
作为交换  我得把网租给唐娜的公司
on the condition that I lease the time to the company where Donna works.
他们需要低廉的价格
They need a competitive price.
卡梅伦的公司
Cameron's company.
越来越复杂了
The plot thickens.
这是戈登的要求
It was Gordon's stipulation.
你知道我会怎么看
You know how this looks.
-是啊  -很糟
- Yeah. - Bad.
这很糟
It looks bad.
我想告诉你的
I would've told you,
但我又想给你看成果
but I wanted to show you the finished product.
的确很傻  但我以为你会觉得我很厉害
It was stupid, but I thought you'd be impressed.
你确实厉害
I am.
我们不要有秘密
We don't keep secrets.
不管多小的秘密  我受不了
I don't care how small. I can't do it.
-早  -早
- Morning. - Morning.
乔  你好啊
Joe, lovely to see you.
唐娜在家吗
Is Donna home?
我不知道你跟她谈是不是个好主意
I'm not sure you really want to talk to her.
唐娜她...
Donna doesn't, uh--
我不知道该怎么说  她不喜欢你
I don't know how to put this-- like you.
唐娜不喜欢你
Donna does not like you.
我得跟她谈谈
I need to speak to her.
好吧
Okay.
戈登  谁来了
Gordon, who was that?
找你的
It's for you.
我安排了你跟雅各布·维勒的会面
I've set up a meeting with Jacob Wheeler.
他想跟你坐下来聊聊
He's looking forward to sitting down with you.
-指名道姓找我吗  -穆特尼的代表
- Me specifically? - A representative from Mutiny.
你是搞硬件的
I thought you were the obvious choice
显然是最佳人选
given your hardware background.
而且我不是卡梅伦
And because I'm not Cameron.
她的话确实有点尴尬  但这不是我来找你的原因
That would be a little awkward, but that's not why I'm here.
乔  这不是我的公司  你得跟她说
Look, Joe, it's not my company. You need to deal with her.
她得做好准备
I expect her to be prepared
并且能公事公办
and I expect her to be professional.
这也事关穆特尼的未来
It's Mutiny's future on the line here, too.
告诉我时间地点  我保证她会过去
You tell me where and when, I'll make sure she shows up.
我昨晚没听见你回家
I didn't hear you come home last night.
我把乔的事告诉了卡梅伦  她大发脾气
Cameron flipped when I told her about Joe.
我只好留下主持局面
I had to stay and hold down the fort.
想吃点午饭吗
Do you want to get some lunch?
也许我们可以一起去接孩子
Maybe we could go pick up the girls together.
你知道我现在忙得多焦头烂额
You know I'm dealing with a lot of stuff right now.
我得回去上班
I-- I have to go back to work.
还得再去跟卡梅伦谈
I have to talk to Cameron, again.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我想先跟你说两句...
I'd like to say a few things before--
他们准备好见我们了吗
Hi, are they ready for us?
稍等片刻
One moment, please.
硬件战争已经结束
The hardware wars are over.
未来属于联络交流
The future is in connection.
穆特尼拥有数款尖端游戏
Mutiny has cutting edge games,
玩家可以在虚拟世界中结识  对抗
people meeting and competing in a virtual world.
韦恩·格雷茨基
据我所知  游戏星球
Sounds like Playnet is doing the same thing,
也在做同样的事
as far as I can tell.
-不  -不
- No. - No?
我们提供的是全面的交互体验
We create a fully interactive experience.
他们只是猜词游戏做得不错
They make a pretty good version of hangman.
我们和游戏星球不一样
We're not doing the same thing as Playnet.
也不想跟他们一样
We don't want to do the same thing as Playnet.
我们在用他们一半的资源做更好的游戏
We're doing something much, much better with half the resources.
-如何实现的  -我们的代码更优化
- And how do you pull that off? - Our code's better.
效率更高  更有创意
It's more efficient and creative.
告诉我  这种事要怎么能做得好
So, tell me, how does someone get good at something like that?
格雷茨基又是怎么打好冰球的
How did Gretzky get good at hockey?
-练习  -还有呢
- Practice. - And?
上天赐予的天赋
And a whole lot of God-given talent.
这可是你说的
It's your words, not mine.
我给你看看吧
Here, let me show you.
没想到你会是冰球迷
I didn't make you for a hockey fan.
我喜欢看打架
I like the fights.
这只是一张演示盘
So this is just a demo disk,
但能让你大概知道
but it'll give you some idea
我们的界面是什么样
of what our interface looks like.
好
Okay.
-学校怎么样  -挺好的
- How was school? - Good.
是吗
Yeah?
想跟爸爸去一起玩吗
You guys wanna go have some fun with your dad?
什么意思
What do you mean?
你们想吧
I don't know. You tell me.
你想做什么都行
We can do anything you want.
我们去外公外婆家
Let's go to Grandma and Grandpa's
-玩电子游戏吧  -好诶
- and play video games! - Yeah!
你们没听明白  我们做什么都可以
You don't understand. We could do anything.
我们可以去公园  去动物园
We could go to the park, we could go to the zoo,
可以去看电影
we could go to the movies, you know?
你们随便说
You name it.
我们去外公外婆家吧
Um, let's go to Grandma and Grandpa's.
你们昨天才去过啊
You guys were just there yesterday.
有点创意嘛  想做什么都行
Come on, be creative. Anything you want, all right?
外婆
Grandma!
-外婆  -这真的不要紧吗  苏珊
- Grandma! - You sure this is all right, Susan?
当然
Of course!
多谢了  我跟她们说去哪都行
I appreciate it. You know, I asked them where they wanted to go,
做什么都可以的
do whatever they want.
她们完全迷上了
They are positively obsessed
盖瑞出差带回来的那东西
with this thing Gary brought back from his trip.
日本人可喜欢他了
The Japs love him.
给了他一台游戏厅的电子游戏
Gave him one of those arcade game video things
可以插电视玩的
you plug into your TV.
要到秋天才发行呢
It's not being released until the fall.
亲爱的  那东西叫什么来着
Hey, sweethearts, what is that contraption called?
-任天堂  -任天堂
- A Nintendo! - Nintendo!
就是一群小人打乌龟还是什么的
It's a bunch of little men fighting turtles or something.
我根本看不懂  真不知有什么好的
I don't-- can't follow it. I don't understand the appeal.
要喝点什么吗
Um, can I offer you a drink?
当然
Sure.
-谢谢  -那好
- Thank you. - Well, great.
不错啊
I'm impressed.
他怎么样呢
So what about this guy?
你们在卡迪夫电子工作时认识的  是吗
You two know each other from your stint at Cardiff Electric, right?
你能替他做担保吗  他要娶我女儿了
Can you vouch for him? He's marrying my daughter.
他是个人物
He's a hell of a guy.
恭喜
Congratulations.
卡梅伦  等等
Uh, Cameron, wait.
我只想说  你刚刚表现很棒
I just wanted to say you were great in there
很高兴能再见到你
and it was nice to see you.
我听说你耍伎俩
You know, when I heard that you had weaseled
回到我生活中来时  我很生气
your way back into my life, I was pissed.
但更多是害怕
But more than that, I was scared
因为我以为我是你的目标
because I thought I was the mark.
他才是  对吗
He's the mark, isn't he?
他不是目标  我不...
He's not a mark. I don't--
这是个实在的生意提议
it's an honest business proposal.
我分不出你是不是知道自己在撒谎
I can't tell if you know you're lying or not.
-我没撒谎  -好吧
- I'm not lying. - Okay.
那么你爱上了
So it's just a coincidence that
一个亿万富翁的女儿只是巧合喽
you fell in love with the daughter of a billionaire.
你为什么不明白我是在帮你
Why can't you see that I'm helping you here?
我没叫你帮忙啊
I never asked for help.
我不需要帮忙  尤其不需要你帮
I don't want any help, especially from you.
听我说  我们分别之后  发生了很多改变
Listen, a lot has changed since I saw you last.
是啊  我不再是那个天真的女孩了
Yeah, I'm not the same naive girl anymore.
离我远点
So just stay away.
你收到我的信了吗
Did you get my letter?
你读了吗
Did you read it?
你就是卡梅伦吧
You must be Cameron.
抱歉  卡梅伦  这是莎拉
Oh, sorry. Cameron, this is Sara.
莎拉  这是卡梅伦
Sara, this is Cameron.
-你未婚妻  当然了  -是啊
- The fiancé, of course. - Yeah.
-恭喜  -谢谢
- Congrats. - Thank you.
乔跟我说了你的公司  真有意思
Uh, Joe told me all about your company. It's very interesting.
我们该一起吃个晚餐
We should all have dinner.
我很想多了解一下
I'd love to learn more about it.
一定的
We'll have to make that happen.
认识你很高兴
Uh, it was lovely to meet you.
乔  很高兴
Joe, always a pleasure.
-一切还好吧  -嗯
- Everything okay? - Yeah.
嗯  很好
Yeah, it was great.
看出来了
Clearly.
你真逗  戈登
You're fun, Gordon.
我以前怎么没发现
How come I never knew you were so much fun?
我是很逗  非常逗
I am fun. I'm super fun.
是唐娜拖我后腿了
It's that Donna that keeps me down.
她是随她爸
She takes after her dad.
我们以前多快乐啊
God, me and her used to have such a good time together.
我们刚在一起的时候  来看你们
You know, when we first got together and we'd come visit you guys,
最后总是去一家酒吧/俱乐部  叫转折
we'd always end up at this bar/club type place, the Twist,
我们一直跳舞到挪不动步
and we would dance till we were just about dead.
简直完爆全场
You know, shut the place down.
-我家唐娜吗  -是啊
- My Donna? - Oh, yeah.
我们搬来的时候
I mean, when we moved here,
我们以为我们会经常去那儿呢
we thought we'd be going there all the time,
但后来  有了孩子了嘛
but, you know, the kids and, you know,
生活忙起来  就忘了找乐子了
life gets in the way and you just forget to have fun.
但玩乐也是很重要的
But, you know, fun's important.
-敬玩乐  -敬玩乐
- To fun. - To fun.
知道吗
You know...
我一直没好好感谢你
I never really thanked you properly.
你和盖瑞对我们太好了
You and Gary have been so good to us.
做了那么多
You know, done so much.
我们好久才站稳脚跟
It took us a while to land on our feet,
但你们一直支持我们
but you supported us throughout.
现在总算有回报了
You know, and now it's finally paid off.
苏珊  没有你我们做不到的
Susan, we couldn't have done it without you.
有钱不帮你爱的人
Well, what's the point of having money
还有什么意义呢
if not to help out your loved ones?
我不是指钱
Well, I don't mean the money.
就是  你们的支持
I just mean, you know, being there for us.
嗯
Yeah.
你希望我还钱吗
Well, what, you want me to pay you back?
我以为...
I thought that's what--
抱歉  这下我不好意思了
I'm sorry, I feel awkward.
你确实希望我还钱吗
Oh, you want me to pay you back?
是你说到家庭和支持
Well, all that talk of family and support
而且你们现在有钱了
and you having money now,
我就是...
I just...
我觉得你喝得有点多了  亲爱的
I think you've had too much to drink, sweetheart.
不不
Oh, no, no, no.
我们欠你们多少钱
What do we owe you?
唐娜永远不欠我们什么
Donna will never owe us a cent.
但是交响乐
But the Symphonic?
我们总共投入了2.2万多
We put in just north of 22,000, all told.
我带支票簿了
I got my checkbook.
你说2.2万多
Uh, just north of 22, 000, you say.
那就写2.3万吧
Why don't we make it an even 23?
我和我闺蜜
You know, my girlfriends and I
我们去试酒  那种事你也知道的
we went on a wine tasting, and you know how that is.
自然而然就发生了
One thing leads to another.
怎么了  什么罪名
What? What was the charge?
不当露体
Indecent exposure.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我简直震惊了
I'm absolutely scandalized.
抱歉  先生  能跟您说句话吗
I'm sorry, sir. Can I speak to you a moment?
当然
Yeah, sure.
就回来
Just one moment.
抱歉  先生  您的卡被拒了
I'm sorry, sir. Your card is declined.
被拒
Declined?
-把经理找来  -我就是
- Let me talk to the manager. - I am the manager.
我以前总来这儿的
Look, I used to come here all the time.
-我跟西尔维奥是朋友  -他退休了
- I'm friends with Silvio. - He retired.
我能付得起的
Look, I'm good for it.
我明天一早就来
I'll be here first thing tomorrow
拿着厚厚一叠钱  给你很多小费
with a fat wad of cash and a hefty tip.
我保证
You have my word.
-不能让她付钱吗  -当然不能
- Well, can't she pay? - No, she cannot pay.
-她是我的女伴  -得了  这都1985年了
- She is my date. - Come on, man. It's 1985.
拜托
Come on.
给我点时间想办法  好吗
Give me a second to work something out, all right?
好吧
All right.
伙计们  切特在用别人的账户登录聊天室
Guys, Chet's entering rooms through other people's accounts
还大骂博斯沃思把他踢出网络
and he's cursing out Bosworth for kicking him off the network.
逗死了
It's hilarious.
穆特尼
Mutiny.
-给  -谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
-嗯  -我回头还你
- Yeah. - I'll pay you back.
嗯  没事  回头见
Yeah, that's cool. I'll see you a little later.
新椅子怎么样
How'd you like your new chair?
你把切特踢出网络了吗
Did you kick Chet off the network?
是啊
Yeah.
为什么啊
Why did you do that?
他欠费了  付不起钱
He was in arrears. He couldn't pay.
你最该同情他了
I think you'd have some sympathy for that.
该死  卡梅伦  拜托  你懂我什么意思
Oh, shit, Cameron, come on, you know what I mean.
是你说他烦人的  这是生意
You said he was a pain in the ass. It's a business.
不  这是个社区
No, it's a community.
我的社区
It's my community.
我们不能随便踢人
And we don't kick people out.
这会让人有想法
It sends a message, okay?
他从一开始就是忠实用户
He's been with us since day one. He's loyal.
是啊  他是烦人  但我喜欢他烦我
Yeah, he's a pain in the ass, but I like being annoyed by him
我喜欢我的破椅子
and I like my shitty chair.
我是希望...别人都别来插手穆特尼
I just... want everyone to leave Mutiny alone.
它是我的
It's mine.
喂
Hello?
是亨利假阳具之家吗
Is this Henry's House of Dildos?
克拉克先生啊
Ah, yes, Mr. Clark.
您订购的超小安全套刚刚到货
Your order of extra small condoms just arrived.
你好吗  汉克
How are you, Hank?
挺好的  伙计  你怎么样
I'm good, buddy. How are you?
还行吧  孩子们怎么样
I'm gettin' by. How are the kids?
臭熏熏  脏兮兮  还顶嘴
They smell terrible, they're filthy, they talk back.
简直待不下去
It's no way to live.
我的女儿是天使
Yeah, well, I got a couple of angels.
-长得像妈妈  -谢天谢地
- Got their mother's looks. - Yeah, thank God for that.
什么事啊  就打来烦我的吗
So, what's up? You just calling to bust some balls or what?
我想去看看你
Well, I was thinking about visiting,
带着我女儿去
you know, bringing the girls.
好啊
That's a great idea.
爸爸妈妈肯定也想见你
I'm sure Mom and Dad would like to see you, too,
如果你乐意开车过去的话
if you want to make the drive over there.
你真希望我过去吗
You really want me to come?
你不是随便说说的
You're not just saying that?
别傻了  我当然欢迎你来
Don't be stupid. Of course I do.
我想死你了  戈登
I miss the hell outta you, Gordo.
聊聊天  叙叙旧  会很棒的
Yeah, it'd be great to talk, catch up.
是啊  一定的
Yeah. Yeah, it would be.
约会怎么样
How was your date?
不怎么样
I've had better.
天呐
God.
我觉得你该跟卡梅伦谈谈
You know, I think you should talk to Cameron.
我觉得她现在有烦心事
I think she's going through some stuff right now
而你能帮上她
I think you could help her with.
什么意思
What do mean?
虽然不管我的事  但我觉得她可能怀孕了
None of my damn business, but I think she might be pregnant.
你为什么会这么想
Uh, why do you think that?
我在后面垃圾桶里发现一个测孕装备
I found a pregnancy kit in the trash out back.
我也不清楚
I don't know.
嗯
Yeah.
不
No, I...
那不是卡梅伦的
it wasn't Cameron's.
恭喜
Congratulations.
谢谢
Thanks.
机器人不会疼
Cyborgs don't feel pain.
我会疼
I do.
别再那么做了
Don't do that again.
-放开我  -听着  听明白了
- Just let me go. - Listen and understand!
终结者还活着
That Terminator is out there.
你没法跟它商量  没法跟它说理
It can't be bargained with, it can't be reasoned with...
-伙计  坐下  -它没有同情心
- Dude, sit down. - ...it doesn't feel pity...
-闪开  -不会感到悔恨  或恐惧
- Move. - or remorse, or fear.
更不会停手
And it absolutely will not stop, ever...
-博迪  让开啊  -直到它杀了你
- Brodie, get out of the way! - ...until you are dead!
好诶
Yeah!
好了  我得走了
All right, I gotta go.
-你去哪  -得走了
- Where you goin'? - Gotta go?
我有约会
I have a date.
而且不是在社区聊天室里
And not in a Community room,
是跟真实  活生生的女人
but with an actual living, breathing woman.
明天见了
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
真棒
Yeah, do it!
玩得开心
Have fun.
看最后一页
Turn to the last page.
-为什么  -看最后一页
- Why? - Just turn to the last page.
乔·麦克米伦
我只想要你
The only thing I'm after is you.
我觉得我们该放慢脚步
I think we need to slow things down.
我觉得这一切太快了
I think it's all going too fast.
我需要点空间想想清楚
I just need some room to figure it out.
-是因为卡梅伦吗  -不  是因为你
- Is this about Cameron? - No, it's about you.
或许也是因为我
And maybe it's about me, too.
我说不清
I don't know.
-我就是需要点时间  -时间  那是什么意思
- I just need some time. - Time? What does that mean?
-我要回奥斯汀  -多久
- I'm going back to Austin. - For how long?
我不知道
I don't know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
就该这么开始
This is how it should start.
让玩家从通风井什么的爬进去
You should have to crawl through a ventilation shaft or something.
我觉得他们信了
I think they bought it.
怎么了
What's wrong?
没事
Nothing.